<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Merry's Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[Merry's Blog using GatsbyJS.]]></description><link>https://d-des.ga</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 12:18:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[About online privacy]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, in these days, we all know that in this kind of generation,
everyone has a gadget to use, commonly used are phones and personal…]]></description><link>https://d-des.ga/about-online-privacy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://d-des.ga/about-online-privacy/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;So, in these days, we all know that in this kind of generation,
everyone has a gadget to use, commonly used are phones and personal
computers. But what about your information?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the internet, you should never ever reveal your personal information
which are sensitive like your credit card, personal ID’s or any kind of
personal identification which are very sensitive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a social media user, you should know how would you share your
information to others, especially if that social media platform involves
the using of usernames, in order to hide or it serves as a cloak from your
real name. Especially &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, a social media platform
which I consider as &lt;strong&gt;“way too personal”&lt;/strong&gt; since we use our real names there.
But Facebook also filters people who are not in your country or even not your
friend’s friend (friends of friends). But in posting, it is recommended that you
do not include your real information there, and/or post something way too personal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I am also a &lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.com&quot;&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt; user, which involves the use of
usernames, chat or talk to people from other countries. And as I have been using
Discord for two years now. I have seen some people use this platform for
malicious use like, selling information through DMs or direct messages
(also termed as PMs or private messages), even distribute malware, still through direct
messages since no one can ban them on servers unless caught and will be reported
to the Discord Team for violating the &lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.com/terms&quot;&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I only share my personal information, not credit card details or alike, to people that
I know, or my friends and to websites that are legitimate in order for verification
purposes and use their services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;tl;dr, don’t ever share your personal information everywhere in the public internet, not
only your information is compromised but your identity also is.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Discord Bot Updates]]></title><description><![CDATA[CodeFactor Rating: CodeFactor So, I tried a third party code analyzer which grades your code
quality and also checks for issues in the…]]></description><link>https://d-des.ga/discord-bot-updates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://d-des.ga/discord-bot-updates/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;CodeFactor Rating: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.codefactor.io/repository/github/daijobudes/daijobuudes&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.codefactor.io/repository/github/daijobudes/daijobuudes/badge&quot; alt=&quot;CodeFactor&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I tried a third party code analyzer which grades your code
quality and also checks for issues in the program.
I did not expect that it was an A+ rating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, I’ve been using &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;flake8&lt;/code&gt; as my linter on &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;vscode&lt;/code&gt; in order
to maintain at least sortableness and also the readability of
the code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New features are, earthquake updates in the Philippines by
getting sources on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://earthquake.phivolcs.dost.gov.ph/&quot;&gt;PHIVOLCS website&lt;/a&gt;
by using &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;BeautifulSoup&lt;/code&gt; library by web scraping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A sample GIF to show that it works!
&lt;img src=&quot;/e4d2cd5f3f309c5037739ca70dc11f56/mGUNIUXvlo.gif&quot; alt=&quot;PHIVOLCS Data&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And also, getting the user details and statistics on
&lt;a href=&quot;https://osu.ppy.sh/home&quot;&gt;osu!&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/7b8e28b4738e0489001188a2b33ba34b/vVR6g902N7.gif&quot; alt=&quot;osu GetUser on Discord&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Discord Bot "daijobuudes"]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actually got bored from doing anything due to this
community quarantine, in order to kill time, I have coded a
discord bot made in Python…]]></description><link>https://d-des.ga/discord-bot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://d-des.ga/discord-bot/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 18:14:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Actually got bored from doing anything due to this
community quarantine, in order to kill time, I have coded a
discord bot made in Python.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I am interested on programming and bots on how they work
and how are they coded. Of course, I made it out of boredom, and it
worked pretty well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My goal for this bot is to use this for moderation, and still
slowly implementing it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, if ever you have a discord server, feel free to invite my bot
using this &lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.com/api/oauth2/authorize?client_id=732431209312944190&amp;#x26;permissions=8&amp;#x26;redirect_uri=http%3A%2F%2Flocalhost&amp;#x26;scope=bot&quot;&gt;OAuth Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since it is open-source, the public repo is
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DaijobuDes/daijobuudes&quot;&gt;here at Github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a preview of the bot.
&lt;img src=&quot;/65a048d602d49448868c93a6580c69a1/x4FIV2JCqX.gif&quot; alt=&quot;GIF&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. My bot is self-hosted, not in any kind of VPS services.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[About this site]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, about this site. It’s currently running on my
Raspberry Pi 4B and is running on
Gatsby JS. So, my site is behind Cloudflare’s Reverse…]]></description><link>https://d-des.ga/about-site/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://d-des.ga/about-site/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 21:54:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;So, about this site. It’s currently running on my
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raspberrypi.org/&quot;&gt;Raspberry Pi 4B&lt;/a&gt; and is running on
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gatsbyjs.org/&quot;&gt;Gatsby JS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, my site is behind &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cloudflare.com&quot;&gt;Cloudflare’s Reverse Proxy&lt;/a&gt; to also hide my
IP address and to enable SSL (HTTPS) on the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, my site has a metrics system enabled and can be viewed on &lt;a href=&quot;https://d-des.ga/netdata&quot;&gt;/netdata&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I’ll write posts that seems interesting in the future to be viewed in the blog.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>